we call Odessa from something else
вызываем одессита то еще
Russian from and make Ukrainian there
российскому от и делать там украинской
so
так
it’s hitler dad ranks a counter blow so
это гитлер папа ряды встречный удар так
it turns out to
выходит
confess to something like that well winter is
повинная на подобное ну тут winter
right here love so it comes out about your
правильно любовь так выходит об вашему
still soloist loveyou napkin we watch
еще солистка loveyou салфетка наблюдаем
sounds
звидки
about me on show ukraine
обо мне на показывай украина
volcano immediately subway
вулкане сразу метро
talk on advice factor
разговаривают на фактор advice
dilute  and of course, the goal is to measure and
разбавлять и разумеется цель измерять и
you asked, diluting the Ukrainian passport of the
вы спросили разбавляя украинский паспорт
series, you understand a
серии понимаете
good dollar,
добрый долл
but this is a dialect of the Russian language, but
но это диалект русского языка а можем
can we put something in a package
можно на в пакет
that can last Ukrainian, we
чему-то может длиться украинскому у нас
used to have Ukrainians 42 million
раньше было так украинца 42 миллиона
Russians and Seychelles British poems
русских и сейшелах британцы стихи
Americans and Australians in Balti you will
американцы и австралийцы в бельцы
appoint  the Australian is
назначишь австралийскому
correct here one turns of the bone wear them lay them down
правильно тут одна витки кости носи их
so the rules could not be
заложи так правил не смог
imperious advice to the cool and the formula
властной advice to the cool и формула
to meddle is the old Slavic so here is
соваться давняя славянскому так тут
Novosibirsk who is alive there Novosibirsk from
новосибирск кто там жив новосибирску от
yours in those hours
вашему в те часы
Russian people are not here these hours Rku thousands of
русские люди не вот эти часы рку тысячи
rocky in that sharks even formed there
рокки в том акулы формировалась там даже
becomes throughout Russia so
становится на всей территории россии так
the array of the topic you didn’t bulo, he was, and here to
массив тема вы не було он и был и тут
litter it’s not like in Russia, so there
засорять же не то что на руси так там
such things were divided into Chernihiv region there
такие вещи на там черниговщина поделили
and
и
he names himself from the Russian word, the Russian word is
он называет самого от русского слова
hardly visible, but the view is
мало на видны вид российское слова а вид
Slavic Old Slavonic experience and yes
славянская старославянском опыт и да
yes to the stars Trotsky  you are a nation to the
да to the stars троцкий вас нация
ancestors of the Ukrainian to him, then we bring
предкам украинской ему то мы своди
something else to the Russian responded to this
что-то еще российскому ответил этому
crisis so
кризис так
nicely and yes, do you last in this e
приятно и да разве ты длится в этом е
Old English and English reshoot
староанглийская и английского переснять
and cardinally
а кардинально
express the Ukrainians step by step the house
выражаете шаг за раз украинцев домовая
mare of thousands of lessons in that and so
кобыла тысяч уроки в том а так-то
here is advice to  maybe we have
вот advice to можем у нас и есть самого
Slavic power ourselves and we have a beautiful
власть на славянская у вас и красиво у
crow here
нас тут ворона
ok olesya I put you with a club in Ukraine
ok олеся я ставлю ты с дубиной в украине
now I don’t understand you I will expose
вот теперь я вас не понял я к выставит
historians to your Stallone with a club in Ukraine
историки ваши сталлоне дубиной в украине
new to advanced Russians with the
новой до продвинутого россиян с
understanding of 6 eggs  let's
разумением 6 яйца давайте так
as you feel
как вы
about Vienna and
относитесь до вены а
war before
войны до
you want slavin war
хочешь славина война
like that time Peter I might ideas of your
как то время петр i might идеи вашего
order so
уряду так
I want
хочу
it was
это был
our office so
наш офис так
each subsequent move
каждый последующий ход
worsens yours  situation
ухудшает твое положение
more deterioration there is less if we
больше ухудшение есть меньше если бы мы
didn’t do anything
ничего не делали
ukraine i think the next
украина я думаю последующем
one who know i’m those shahid you understand the age of the
кто знаете я вот тех шахид разумеешь век
show in russia zugzwang so you sincerely
шоу у россии цугцванг так ты искренне
read the parask
читая параска
sound 50 countries guides on solving the
зазвучать 50 стран гайды по решения
situation so in position and sadder the
ситуации так на позиции и печальнее
result here let’s say here I am to  respects
результат вот скажем вот я к уважает и
to the pitt the idea that we don’t need
to the pitt думку тем что мы не треба
brightness defend myself, I’ll attack
яркость защищайтесь я нападу печь так
the furnace so that’s how Russia acted like Hitler
так то россия поступила так самая гитлер
did and the course
так и ход
of Napoleon’s war,
войны
whether Putin is like that, but we don’t love songs,
ли путин так но удавиться мы не песни
but
любит а
equity is the law, but it sounds well, that’s what
equity закон но звучит ну вот в чем
polished from the law  war to
полируются из закон войны
prevent meetings, yes
предупредить встречи ну да
.  it's hitler dad happy counter blow
. это гитлер папа рады встречный удар
so it turns out
так выходит
she confessed well here winter
повинной она подала ну тут winter
work properly comes out about your
правильно работать выходит об вашему
nothing whistle loveyou napkin is
ничего свистка loveyou салфетка добр а
kind otherwise they kizu a terrible blow ukraine strike a little
то они kizu страшный удар украина мало
russia
наносите россии
ukraine strike
украина
it a little here will show you
наносите его на мало вот выкажет вы по
passed out an oyster blow
передал из устричный удар
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
in Russian, how do I, in Russian, the swamis
по русски как я же по-русски свами
seem with the towers, the seams endure the shock 20
кажутся с вышками швы выноси шок 20
makes the Ukrainian mov
делает украинской мовы
bachata, you still can’t you knife
бачаты вы все-таки не может вы ножевыми
words and
словен и
tag
тег